Rebecca Adamson Papers, 1979-2007
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES III. PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES, [See also Restricted materials in box 51]
  - First Nations Development Institute
    - Eagle Staff Fund
      - Procedures manual 1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Economic Development Service: business plan 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Field Operations
      - General 1987-89, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Midwest Field Office 1986-90 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Northwest Field Office 1987-89, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - South Dakota Field Office (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Affiliated Tribes of Northwest Indians
        - General 1983, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
        - Economic Development Committee 1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
        - Technical Assistance Project: application to U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development 1987, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 13-14)
      - Central Council Tlingit and Haida Tribes of Alaska, Tináa Corporation 1989-94 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Cherokee Community Loan Fund 1989-90, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Cherokee Nation Economic Development discussion 2001 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Confederated Tribes of the Grand Ronde Indians 1982-83, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Confederated Tribes of the Siletz Indians 1988-89 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Confederated Tribes of the Umatilla Indian Reservation
        - General 1987-92, undated (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
        - "Land Acquisition Program of the Umatilla Tribes" circa 1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
        - "The Umatilla Tribes' Land Acquisition and Consolidation Project" undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Fort Belknap Community Council 1987-88, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Kickapoo Tribe of Kansas 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Klamath Tribe 1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Kodiak Area Native Association (KANA)
        - General 1985-89, undated (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
        - Overall Economic Development Program: packet for visit Nov 1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
        - Port Lions Tribal Council, Kizhuyak Oil Sales Project
          - General 1988-89, undated (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
          - Community Development Block Grant-Rural Economic Development Initiative (CDBG-REDI) Application circa 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
        - Sea Otter Commission and marine mammal regulations 1988-89 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Kodiak Area Native Association (KANA)
        - Tribal Enrollment/Community Development Conference pamphlet 1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Lac du Flambeau Tribe 1981 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Mattaponi-Pamunkey-Monacan Consortium 1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Meherrin Indian Group 1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Minnesota Chippewa Tribe
        - General 1980-82, undated (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
        - Business Support Services 1981 (Box 8, Folder 10)
        - Publication, "Investment Principles: What You Need to Know to Manage Your Tribe's Investments," 1994 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Navajo Nation
        - Adah Community Loan Association 1993-94 (Box 8, Folder 12)
        - Ramah Navajo Weavers Association 1984-89, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
        - Shiprock Agency Reservation Economic Impact Study (REIS) 1992-93, undated (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
      - Northern Circle Indian Housing Authority 1993 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Oglala Sioux Tribe
        - General 1987-89, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
        - Brotherhood Community Health Clinic/Porcupine Clinic
          - General 1982-92, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
          - Brotherhood Community Health Board 1989-91 (Box 9, Folder 3)
          - Business and Operating Plan 1989-93 by FNFP, Sep 1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
          - First Nations agreements, reports, and work plans 1987-93, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
          - Funding proposals
            - Bush Foundation 1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
            - Northwest Area Foundation 1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
            - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
        - Little Wound Financial Self-Sufficiency Project
          - General 1981-84, nd.. (Box 9, Folder 9)
          - Adamson report undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
          - Little Wound School Traveling Art Exhibit, 1983, undated
            - General (Box 9, Folder 11)
            - Student art (Box 9, Folder 12)
            - Notebook (Box 9, Folder 13)
        - Makoce Institute 1985-86, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
        - Maternal/Child Health Consortium Program: proposal 1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
        - Nebraska Sioux Lean Beef, Inc. 1986, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
        - Oglala Lakota College
          - General 1981-83, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
          - FNFP 1983-84 (Box 10, Folder 3)
        - Oglala Sioux Parks and Recreation Authority Financial Self-Sufficiency Administration for Native Americans (ANA) proposal 1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
        - Pine Ridge Reservation
          - General 1983-1986, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
          - Research by Richard Sherman, National Rural Fellow 1986-87 (Box 10, Folder 6)
        - Tiospaye Project 1987, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Rosebud Sioux Tribe
        - General 1982-90, undated (Box 10, Folder 8-11)
        - Expenditure survey 1989-90, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Saginaw Chippewa Indian Tribe of Michigan, [see also Publications]
        - General 1983-90, undated (Box 11, Folder 1-4)
        - Administration for Native Americans (ANA) grant 1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
        - "An Economic Development Plant for the Saginaw Chippewa Community, Mount Pleasant, Michigan," James M. Murray and Charles F. Wheelock undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
        - Hearing re Senate 1106 10 Jul 1985 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Samish Indian Tribe of Washington 1983-88, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Shawnee Nation United Remnant Band 1990 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Shinnecock Reservation 1982-92 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Spokane Tribe of Indians 1982-82, 1986-87 (Box 11, Folder 11-12)
      - Swinomish Indian Tribal Community undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Texas Band of Kickapoo 1987-88 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Tlingit and Haida Indian Tribes of Alaska 1989-92 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Umatilla, [see Confederated Tribes of the Umatilla Indian Reservation] (Box 11)
      - United South and Eastern Tribes, Inc. (USET) 1983-86 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Upper Skagit Indian Tribe 1982-87 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Winnebago Tribe of Nebraska 1982-90, undated (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
      - Yankton Sioux Tribe 1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Financial, [see also Lakota Fund below]
      - General 1984-93 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Audit report 1990 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Fundraising
        - General 1995-2001, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
        - Europe trips 1997, 1999 9-10 Educational Tour of Alaska for Grantmakers, Rasmuson Foundation, Aug 1999 (Box 12)
        - Funders' Tour of Arizona and New Mexico Oct 1998 (Box 12, Folder 12)
        - Fundraising letters undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
        - Fundraising plan 1989 (Box 12, Folder 14)
        - David and Lucille Packard Foundation 2000 (Box 12, Folder 15)
        - F.B. Heron Foundation 2000 (Box 12, Folder 16)
        - Ford Foundation 1999-2001, [see also Lakota Fund] (Box 13, Folder 1)
        - Northwest Area Foundation 1989 (Box 13, Folder 2)
        - Open Society Institute 2000 (Box 13, Folder 3)
        - West coast trip 1998 (Box 13, Folder 4)
        - Proposals
          - MacArthur Foundation: "FNFP Institutional Strategy," 1987 (Box 13, Folder 5)
          - M.J. Murdock Charitable Trust: "Indians Developing Economic Action Strategies (IDEAS)" circa 1989-90 (Box 13, Folder 6)
          - First Nations Funders' Collaborative circa 1992 (Box 13, Folder 7)
          - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, "Building a Foundation for First Nations Development" circa 1998 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - First Nations Arts 1993-95, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Forms (blank) undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Grant approval process 1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Human Economics in Action Program (HEAP)
      - General 1989-90, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Hannahville Indian Community 1985, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Michigan
        - General 1985-86, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
        - Keweenah Bay Indian Community 1984, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
        - Western Upper Peninsula Regional Planning and Development Commission Overall Economic Development Program 1984 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Lakota Fund, [see also Reports by Gerald Sherman, Elsie Meeks]
      - General
        - 1985-88 (Box 13, Folder 17)
        - 1989-93, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Project proposal drafts 1986-87, undated (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
      - Articles of incorporation and by-laws 1985-87, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Board and committees
        - General 1985-87, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
        - Interviews 1986 (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
      - Board of Directors
        - General 1986-92, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
        - Training Program 1986, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Business Plan 1991-92 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Circle Banking Project
        - General undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
        - Staff visit to Grameen Bank 1988-89 (Box 14, Folder 13-14)
        - Article for Business Alert, "Microenterprise Lending: The Lakota Fund/Grameen Bank Experience," by Gerald Sherman 1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
        - "Micro-Enterprise Lending Manual," 1989 (Box 15, Folder 2)
        - Newsletter 1991-93 (Box 15, Folder 3)
        - Orientation Training packet undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
        - Proposal to Mott Foundation 1991 (Box 15, Folder 5)
        - Reference file: Grameen Bank 1983-90, undated (Box 15, Folder 6-7)
      - Community Education Project 1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence 1985-93, undated (Box 15, Folder 9-12)
      - Consultants' reports
        - Haydn Anthony 1992 (Box 15, Folder 13)
        - Susan Reynolds 1992 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Financial
        - General 1987-92, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
        - Accounting circa 1987 (Box 15, Folder 16)
        - Financial statements 1988-92 (Box 15, Folder 17)
        - Offering memorandum 1987 (Box 16, Folder 1)
        - Pro forma financial statements 1986-89, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
        - Bush Foundation 1987, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
        - Campaign for Human Development 1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
        - Ford Foundation
          - General 1985-93, undated (Box 16, Folder 5-13)
          - Loan
            - Agreement 1987 (Box 17, Folder 1)
            - Closing binder 22 Dec 1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
            - Fund Management letter 25 Nov 1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
        - Ms. Foundation for Women 1991-92 (Box 17, Folder 4)
        - Needmor Fund 1988 (Box 17, Folder 5)
        - Northwest Area Foundation 1988-92 (Box 17, Folder 6)
        - Northwest Bank 1989 (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - Promissory notes and loan agreements [loans to Lakota Fund] 1987-93, undated (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
      - Loans by Lakota Fund
        - General 1986, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
        - Business proposals 1986 (Box 17, Folder 11)
        - Loan summaries and status reports 1987-90 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Market Analysis 1986 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Peer Review Report, National Association of Community Development Loan Funds Jan 1992 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Staff
        - General 1989, 1991, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
        - Fund Manager Search 1986 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Technical Assistance undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Legal
      - General 1986-89 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Rosenfelt, Barlow & Borg
        - Dec 1988- Apr 1989 (Box 17, Folder 19)
        - May-Dec 1989, undated (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
    - Marketing Program 1987-91, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Native American Health Concept Paper Apr 1996 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Office: special use permit 1988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Oweesta Program, [see also Lakota Fund]
      - General 1986-89 (Box 18, Folder 6-10)
      - Conferences
        - "Managing Tribal Assets," 4th Annual Oweesta Conference 21-24 Mar 1993 (Box 18, Folder 11)
        - "Building From Within: Development Towards Independence" 22-25 May 1995 (Box 18, Folder 12)
        - 1997 (Box 18, Folder 13)
        - Pre-Conference Session, "Indigenous Economics" slides from presentation by Rebecca Adamson 1998 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Policy and Advocacy Program
      - General 1991 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Issue Paper: Credit and Financing undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Issue Paper for Indian Land Consolidation Legislation 1995, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Policy analysis
        - "Doing Business: An Evaluation of Policy Alternatives to Encourage Private Enterprise on Indian Reservations" by Eric M. Rice Jul 1989 (Box 19, Folder 5)
        - "Satisfying the Political Subdivision and Integral Part Tests," Legal analysis of IRS Code Section 7871 by Gardner, Carton & Douglas 1999 (Box 19, Folder 6)
        - "Tribal Responses to Federal Land Consolidation Policy" by Margo S. Miller Apr 1988 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Publications
      - General 1991, 1994, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Artwork and design undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - "Arts and Crafts Business Directory": proof undated (Box 19, Folder 10-16)
      - "Building Our Knowledge: Indigenous Economics" curriculum 1995 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - "Business Alert" (miscellaneous issues) 1986, 1993-95 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - "Controlling Consulting: A Manual for Native American Governments and Organizations," by Idrian N. Resnick Mar 1990 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - "First Nations Arts" catalog, n.d (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - "Investing for the Future: How the Saginaw Chippewa Put Their Capital to Work"
        - May 1989 (Box 20, Folder 3)
        - Sep 1993 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - "Reservation-Based Loan Funds Manual" by Larry Swift
        - Draft 1988 (Box 20, Folder 5)
        - 1989 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - "Tribal Marketing Casebook" by Ann Posner 1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - "Tribal Marketing Management" by Rebecca Adamson and Rosalie Good Bear, Illustrations by Janet Sillaway: paste up
        - Version 1 (Box 20, Folder 8-9)
        - Version 2 (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
    - Reports
      - Annual 1985, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Biennial 1986-87, 1996-97, 1998-99, 2000-01 (Box 21, Folder 5-7)
      - Twenty Year Report 2000 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Highlights/Activities reports 1987-89, 1991-93 (Box 21, Folder 9-12)
      - "Information on Business codes, law and transactions on Indian Reservations," Theresa Carmody Apr 1986 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - "Summary, Issues, and Comments on the Price-Waterhouse In-Depth Review of Indian Trust Funds for the Bureau of Indian Affairs, U.S. Department of the Interior," by Carol Aman, Oman Financial Services Jun 1986 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - "Evaluation of Reservation-Based Loan Programs," David H. Festa and James R. St. George, Harvard Project on Indian Economic Development May 1988 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - "Trust: A Matter of Control-A Report on Tribal Trust Fund Management and Opportunities for Increased Tribal Control" Oct 1988 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - "Options for Developing a Business and Investment Fund on the Flathead Indian Reservation" prepared for the Confederated Salish and Kootenai Tribes of the Flathead Nations by FNDI Sep 1991 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - "Overview of National Indian Organizations" circa 1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - "Research on Developing a Land Acquisition Finance Mechanism" by Theresa Carmody Feb 1992 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - "Native Communities: Persistent Obstacles to an Open Society" 2000, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous 2000, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Staff
        - Monthly Jul 1981-83, 1986, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 7-10)
        - Quarterly 1981-84 (Box 22, Folder 11-13)
        - Sandra Abrams 1992-93 (Box 22, Folder 14-15)
        - Rebecca Adamson: monthly reports 1993 (Box 22, Folder 16)
        - Sherry Salway Black 1988-92 (Box 22, Folder 17-21)
        - Theresa Carmody, Policy/Advocacy Office 1985-94 (Box 23, Folder 1-11)
        - Karen Charleston, Management Intern 1988 (Box 23, Folder 12)
        - Elouise C. Cobel 1990-92 (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
        - Andrea Cooper, Office Manager 1990-92 (Box 24, Folder 4-5)
        - Andrea Coron 1992-94 (Box 24, Folder 6-9)
        - Kristin Coron, Marketing 1992-94 (Box 24, Folder 10-12)
        - Gini Egan[-McKenna], Research Consultant 1990-91 (Box 24, Folder 13)
        - Dennis R. Fox, Jr., Marketing 1993-94 (Box 24, Folder 14-15)
        - Pamela Frye 1988 (Box 24, Folder 16)
        - Jo Lynn Gentry, Policy Specialist 1989-90 (Box 24, Folder 17)
        - Marcella Burgess Giles, Research and Data Bank 1990 (Box 24, Folder 18)
        - Steven Haberfeld, Consultant 1989-91 (Box 24, Folder 19)
        - Laura Henze, Oweesta Consultant
          - 1988 (Box 24, Folder 20)
          - 1989-90 (Box 25, Folder 1-3)
        - Debra Hill 1989-91 (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
        - Diane Hogsed, Finance 1989-90 (Box 25, Folder 6)
        - Chuck Jacobs 1985-87 (Box 25, Folder 7-8)
        - Mark R. Jacobson, Development Office 1987-90 (Box 25, Folder 9-11)
        - Samantha Kaplan 1992-93 (Box 25, Folder 12-13)
        - Bruce King 1990-91 (Box 25, Folder 14)
        - Pamela Kinney 1991, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 15)
        - Angela Lawson 1989 (Box 25, Folder 16)
        - Deb Levy 1989 (Box 25, Folder 17)
        - Annie Mayo 1994 (Box 25, Folder 18)
        - Bruce McKay 1993 (Box 25, Folder 19)
        - Elsie Meeks, Technical Assistance Specialist, Lakota Fund 1986-92, [see also Gerald Sherman] (Box 25, Folder 20)
        - Phyliss Minn 1992-93 (Box 25, Folder 21-22)
        - Patrick Murphy, Midwest Field Office 1988 (Box 26, Folder 1)
        - Robert Cloud North, Marketing 1992 (Box 26, Folder 2)
        - Bonnie Paquin 1994 (Box 26, Folder 3)
        - Tonya Parker, Policy and Advocacy 1990-91 (Box 26, Folder 4)
        - Janet Place, Consultant 1993 (Box 26, Folder 5)
        - Ann Posner 1988-89, [see also Pourier] (Box 26, Folder 6)
        - Lori Lea Pourier, Marketing 1985-91 (Box 26, Folder 7-12)
        - Jerry Reynolds 1993-94 (Box 26, Folder 13)
        - Susan Reynolds, Consultant to Lakota Fund 1992 (Box 26, Folder 14)
        - Mike Roberts 1992-93 (Box 26, Folder 15-16)
        - Randy Ross, Minority Arts Administration Fellowship Intern 1989-90 (Box 26, Folder 17)
        - Gerald Sherman, Lakota Fund 1987-89, [see also Elsie Meeks] (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
        - Richard Sherman, Regional Planner 1989 (Box 27, Folder 4)
        - Andrea Smith, Midwest Field Specialist 1988-91 (Box 27, Folder 5-7)
        - Cris Stainbrook, Northwest Area Office 1988-89 (Box 27, Folder 8-10)
        - Larry D. Swift, Finance Policy Specialist 1985-90 (Box 27, Folder 11-13)
        - Laurie Thompson 1992-94 (Box 28, Folder 1-5)
    - Research and Data Bank undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Staff (Box 28)
      - Evaluation Committee 1994 (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
      - Meetings 1986-90 (Box 28, Folder 9-13)
      - Sherry Salway Black
        - General 1991, 1995, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
        - Speeches, presentations, and writings
          - "The Movement Towards Economic Independence in Indian Country: How Do We Meet the Challenge of Preparing Indian People to Join Movement and Lead the Way?" 1986 (Box 28, Folder 15)
          - "Culturally Appropriate Curricula" 1996 (Box 28, Folder 16)
          - "Envisioning a Healthy Economy in Indian Country" 1996 (Box 29, Folder 1)
          - "Redefining Success in Community Development: A New Approach for Determining and Measuring the Impact of Development" 1994 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Theresa Carmody: "Tribes Building Permanent Homelands," Tribal College Journal 1996 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Debra Levy: "Perspectives in International Development" 1993 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Marian Quinlan: "Part II: Funding the Future," NTEC Tribal Vision 1997 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Survey: Nonprofits in Indian Country 1996 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Tribal Commerce and Enterprise Program (TCEP)/Tribal Commerce and Enterprise Management Program (TCEMP) (Box 29)
      - General 1982-92, undated (Box 29, Folder 7-9)
      - Information requests 1985-86, 1992-93 (Box 29, Folder 10-11)
      - Notes and timelines 1985-86 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Proposal to Carnegie Foundation circa 1983 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - TCEP Program proposal undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Addendum to TCEP proposal circa 1984 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Screening and Selection Committee 1986 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Yale School of Management
        - General 1983-86, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
        - Proposals circa 1983-84 (Box 29, Folder 18-19)
        - Letter of Agreement 1984 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Wilma Mankiller Trust Fund 1990 (Box 29, Folder 21-22)
  - First Peoples Worldwide (Box 29)
    - General 1997-2007 (Box 30, Folder 1-9)
    - Advisory Committee meeting, Kautokeino, Norway 13-16 Apr 2001 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Australia trip 1998 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Biotech Roundtable, New York University 17-18 May 2001 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - First People of the Kalahari and Kwe People, Botswana 1996-97 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Fundraising dinner 14 Nov 2000 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Mark Plotkin, ethnobotanist 2001 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- SERIES IV. ORGANIZATION FILES
  - Miscellaneous 1991-94, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Akwe:kon Journal, Editorial Board 1994-96, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - American Indian Trade and Development Council circa 1988 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Arizona Community Foundation 1994-98, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - The Body Shop, International Human Rights Award Jury 1999 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Calvert Group, Board of Trustees 1990-2001, undated (Box 31, Folder 9-11)
  - Community Development Venture Capital Alliance 1994-95 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Corporation for Enterprise Development 1993-2001 (Box 31, Folder 13-14)
  - Council on Foundations (Box 31)
    - General 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Handbook 1997 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Strategic Planning Resource Materials 1998 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Earth Day 2000 Network, Board of Directors (Box 32)
    - General 1999-2002, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Board packet Sep 1999 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Harvard Project on American Indian Economic Development circa 1988 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Hauser Center for Nonprofit Organizations, Harvard University 1999-2002 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Independent Sector (Box 32)
    - General 1994-2000, undated (Box 32, Folder 8-9)
    - Annual meeting Oct 1995 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Annual meeting and Conference 2001 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors meetings Apr 1996, Apr 1998 (Box 33, Folder 2-3)
    - Evaluation Committee
      - General 1994 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - National Forum on the Vision of Evaluation 1994 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Leadership Committee: meeting packet Nov 1996 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Transition/Search Committee 1994 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Indian Dispute Resolution Services, Inc. 1993-95 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - International Funders for Indigenous Peoples 2001 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Little Wound School, Kyle, South Dakota undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Ms. Foundation for Women 1988, 1991-99 (Box 34, Folder 2-4)
  - National Center for American Indian Enterprise Development
    - General 1989, 1993-94 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Board/Council meeting packet Sep 1993 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - "How to Start a Reservation Enterprise" Nov 1989 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - National Center for Family Philanthropy 2001 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy 1993-97, undated (Box 34, Folder 9-10)
  - National Rural Tourism Foundation 1995 (Box 34, Folder 11-12)
  - Native American Fundraising Project 1994-95 (Box 35, Folder 1)